Ralph E. Flanders Papers
Ralph E. Flanders Papers
- General correspondence files
  - General correspondence, 1938-1939
    - Harriman, Henry I. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Harriman, W. Averell (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Harris & Ewing (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Harvard University (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Harvey, Elbert A. (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Hathaway, George G. (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Hay-Adams House (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Hensen, H. C. (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Herron, James H. (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Hersam. Conrad O. (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Heyniger, C. L. (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Heywood, Johnson (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Hillman, Sidney (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Himbert, Arthur R. (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Hinton, William (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Holman, Charles W. (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Hook, James W. (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Hopkins, Harry (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Horner, Leonard S. (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Hotels, English, Receipts of (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Hough, Ulysses B. (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Howard Relief Society (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Howie, David H. (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Howland, Fred A. (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Hubbard, Guy (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Hurd, Archibald C. (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Hutchinson, Ely (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Industrial Power (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Institute of American Genealogy (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Institute for Applied Social Analysis (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Institute of Student Aid (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - International Business Machines Corporation (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - International Industrial Relations Institute (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - International Management Congress (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - International Management Congress, Fairfield Raymond (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - (7th) International Management Congress (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Interseminary Committee for Training Rural Ministry (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Jackson, Dugald C. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Javits & Javits (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Jeidels, Otto (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Jenkins, C. E. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Jensen, E. Willard (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Jewett, Frank B. (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Johnson, Mrs. Marion B. (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - The Junto (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Kier, E. H. (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Kendall, Henry P. (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Kent, Fred I. (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Kimball, Dexter S. (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Kiplinger, Willard M. (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Kurn Hattin Homes (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Lamson & Sessions Company (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Landon, Alfred M. (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - LaSalle Extension University (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Lawrence, E. F. (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Leeds, Morris E. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - LeLand & Gray Seminary (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, Mrs. Sinclair (Dorothy Thompson) (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Lippman, Walter (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Lovely, John E. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - McCullough, Hall Park (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - McGann, Mrs. Marion (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - McGraw-Hill Company (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - McIntosh, H. M. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Machinery Industrial Press (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Machinery and Allied Products Institute (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - MacLennan, J. F. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Mason, Hason, Harold (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Massachusetts Conference of Social Work (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology
      - Corporation Minutes (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Visiting Committee (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - [General] (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - [General] (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts State Planning Board (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Meredith, L. Douglas (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Merritt, Joseph (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Middlebury College (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Miller, Ted (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Mills, Charles (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Mitchell, Karl M. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Mitchell, Wesley C. (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - National Aeronautic Association (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - National Association of Manufacturers (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - National Association of Purchasing Agents (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - National Bureau of Standards (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - National Conference on Planning (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - National Economic League (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - National Emergency Council (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - National Founders Association (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - National Industrial Conference Board (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - National Industrial Information Committee (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - National Life Insurance Company (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - National Mediation Board (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - National Old Ironsides Patriotic Association (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - National Policy Committee (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - National Resources Committee (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - National Resources Planning (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - National Shawmut Bank (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - National Survey (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - National Youth Administration (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Nelson, Donald (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - New England Council (Box 58, Folder 10-11)
    - New England Town Hall (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - New Hampshire, University of (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - New School for Social Research (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Newark College of Engineering (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Newcomen Society (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Nichols, W. W. (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Nienstaedt, L. R. (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Norris, Alfred G. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Norwich University (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Norwich University-Committee on Faculty Pensions (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Oakley, John W. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - O'Brien, Eugene W. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - O'Mahoney, Joseph C. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - O, General (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Padgett, J. E. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Page, Guy M. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Paine, Ernest T. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Park, F. A. (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Parkhurst, Lewis (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Parkinson, J. F. (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Patterson, Teele & Dennis (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Payne, Roger (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Peeke, George N. (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Pennoyer, Charles H. (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania, University of (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Polish Relief Fund (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Potter, Merle S. (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Power & Works Engineer (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Power Plant Engineering (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Princeton University (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Proctor, Mortimer R. (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Public Works Administration (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Puchstein, Hans (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Putney School (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - P, General (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Ramsey, George (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Reid, Mrs. Helen Rogers (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Riddle, J. H. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Robertson, Andrew W. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Rosenstock-Huessy, Eugene (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Rukeyer, Merryle S. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Rustgard, John (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Rutland Herald (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Sargent, Osgood & Roundy Company (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Schaurte, Werner T. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Schell, Erwin H. (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Science Service (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Seebauer, George (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Shepardson, F. W. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Sherman, Roger (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Siegfried, Thorwald (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Sinsabaugh, R. W. (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Slayton, Ronald (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Slichter, Sumner (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Sloan, George A. (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Alexander H. (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Smith, Blackwell (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Smith, Harold V. (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Smith, Richard R. (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Society for Advancement of Management (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Society for Promotion of Engineers Education (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - "Spice-of-the-Week" (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Sprague, Oliver, M. W. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Springfield Cooperative Savings & Loans (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Springfield High School (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Stettinius, Edward R. Jr. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Stevens Institute (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Stewart, Warren & Benson (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Stiles, R. W. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Stoughton, A. F. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Stuart, Will O. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Stubbs, Norman (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Student Christian Movement (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Student Peace Service at Cambridge (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Survey Associates (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Swart, Duntze & Company (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Sweet Briar College (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Swift & Company (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Swope, Gerard (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Tax Policy League (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Taylor, Edward J. (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Taylor, Myron C. (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Teagle, Walter C. (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Thomasville Chair Company (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Thompson, Dorsey (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Thompson, Sanford E. (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Thrift & Security Foundation (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Tilton, L. B. (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Toward Full Employment (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Town Meeting of the Air (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Treadway, Mrs. Minnie H. (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Tufts College (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Tuskegee Institute (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Tuttle, Morton C. (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Twentieth Century Fund (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Unemployment Book (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - United Farmers' Cooperative Creamery (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - United States Commissioner of Patents (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - United States Customs Service (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - United States Department of Agriculture (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - United States Department of Commerce (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - United States Department of Labor (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - United States Department of Labor Federal Committee on Apprenticeship (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - United States Senate (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - United States Treasury Department (Box 62, Folder 10-11)
    - University Club, Boston (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - University Club, Baltimore, Maryland (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Utah State Historical Society (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Vassar College (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Vermont Congregational Conference (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Vermont Conservation and Development Board (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Vermont Craftsmen (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Vermont Farm Security Administration (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Vermont Federation of Women's Club (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Vermont Guild of Old Time Crafts (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Vermont Guild of Old Time Crafts and Industries (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Vermont Motor Vehicle Department (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Vermont Savings Bank (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Vermont Senate (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Vermont Society of Engineers (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Vermont State Chamber of Commerce (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Vermont State Farm Bureau (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Vermont Structural Slate Company (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Vermont State, various departments (Box 63, Folder 16-17)
    - Vermont, University of (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Von Haan, Baron Hugo (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Waldron, Frederick (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Wall, Alexander C. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Walter, C. Wood (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Washburn, Henry S. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Waterbury High School (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Waterman, Sterry R. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Watertown Times (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Wellesley College (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Wernette, Philip (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Westcott, Harry (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Weston Material (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Whelden, C. H. (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Wilgus, William Col. (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Williams, Elizabeth T. (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Williams, John H. (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Williams, Nathan Boone (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Williams, Mrs. Norman (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Williams, S. Clay (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Williamson, W. A. (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Windels, Paul (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Windsor Mountain School (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Wolman, Leo (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Wood, R. E. (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Woodruff, Caroline S. (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Works Progress Administration (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - World's Fair of 1939 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Wright, Brown, Quinby & May (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - W, General (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Yale Daily News (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Yale Review (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Yale University (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - The Yankee (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Yeomans, Edward (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Young, Robert D. (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Young Republican Club (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Young Women's Christian Association of Burlington (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - General correspondence, 1940-1942
    - Autobiographical sketch, Ralph E. Flanders (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Boston News Bureau (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Chase National Bank (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Christmas Cards Received (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Christmas Cards Sent (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Community House (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Cycle for Chaser & Form Grinder (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of Boston (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - First Congregational Church in Springfield, Vermont (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - First National Bank in Springfield, Vermont (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Fleck, John J. (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Foster, William (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Franklin Institute (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - French, E. S. (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Geier, Frederick (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Gries Reproducer Corporation (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Harriman, Henry I. (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Linde Air Products Company (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Lindeman Power Equipment Company (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Office of Price Administration (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Office of War Information (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Ogden, Sam (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Ohio State University (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Pamphlets for Political Campaign (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Radio Talk, "My Record" (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Rand, Julian R. (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Rath & Strong (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Rucker, Dr. Julius (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - State Street Research and Management Company (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - "Steel", Penton Building, Cleveland, Ohio (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Thompson, Dorsey (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - United States Department of Labor (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - United States Department of State (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - United States Machine Tool Coordinating Commission (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - United States War Department (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Vermont Guild of Old Time Crafts (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Vermont State Planning Board (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Weeks, Arthur B. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Willkie, Wendell L. (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Engineering resource files
  - [General], 1903-1914 (Box 67, Folder 1-12)
  - [General], 1915-1930 (Box 68, Folder 1-13)
  - [General], 1931 (Box 69, Folder 1-14)
  - [General], 1932 (Box 70, Folder 1-19)
  - [General], 1932 (Box 71, Folder 1-18)
- Business correspondence Ffles
  - Business correspondence, 1931-1933
    - American Academy of Political and Social Science (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - American Council on Education (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - American Economic Association (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - American Engineering Council
      - Comment on Report (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Digest of Criticisms (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Economic Balance Committee (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Programs of Work (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Reviews of Plans (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - American Society of Civil Engineering (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers
      - Davis, C. E. (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Hagemann, George E. (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Hall, James W. (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Lauer, C. M. (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Rice, Calvin W. (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Stetson, George A. (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Wetter, Pierce T. (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Local Sections (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - American Society of Refrigerating Engineers (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Ames, Adelbert, Jr. (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Anderson, Benjamin M. (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Beal, Harry S. (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Chase, Stewart (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Chesterman, F. J. (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Cincinnati, University of (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Compton, Karl T. (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Davis, Harvey (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Day, Edmund E. (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Dennison, Henry S. (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - Dewey, Davis R. (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Dewey, John (Box 72, Folder 32)
    - Economic Forum (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Engineering Fund Planning Committee (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Filene, A. Lincoln (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - French, E. S. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Gow, J. Steele (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Gray, William R. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Hall, Arnold Bennett (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Hall, James A. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Hammond, Alonzo J. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Hammond, H. P. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Harbord, J. G. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Harrington, John Lyle (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Harwood, E. C. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Hay, W. W. (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Hays, W. B. (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Hayward, Sidney C. (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Heald, Richard A. (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Heine, Gregor H. (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Henry, D..C. (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Hindley, Howard L. (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Hirschfeld, C. F. (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Hitchcock, Dal (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Hogan, John R. (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Holley, Horace (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Holman, Charles W. (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Hook, James W. (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Hopkins, Ernest M. (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Hudson, Ray M. (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Iron Age (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Jackson, Dugald C. (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Jones, Basset (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Jordan, Virgil (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Kellogg & Company (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Kellogg, Paul U. and Arthur (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Kent, Fred W. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Kilborne, R. D. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Kimball, Dexter S. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - King, Loyal L. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - King, Willford I. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Kiplinger Washington Agency (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Knapp, Ora (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Knight, Harry C (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Ladue, Pomroy (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Lafollette, Robert M., Jr. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Lahee, Arnold W. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Lauer, Conrad H. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Leach, Henry Goddard (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Lee, William S. (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Leeds, Morris E. (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Lehman Corporation, The (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Lennox, John S. (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Levene, Alexander (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Lewis, Herbert B. (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Lippmann, Walter (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Lloyd, T. C. (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Locke, Ione E. (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Lorwin, Lewis L. (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Luten, Daniel B. (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Lyon, L. S. (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - Lytle, Charles W. (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - MacIntire, James (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - Macmillan Company (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Mallery, Otto T. (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Maphis, Charles G. (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - Marks, Lionel S. (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - Marshall, R. C., Jr. (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Martin, E. F. (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Matschoss, Conrad (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - McDonald, Frederick H. (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - McGraw-Hill Company (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - McKibben, W. E. (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - McMichael, L. D. (Box 74, Folder 40)
    - Miller, Fred J. (Box 74, Folder 41)
    - Mitchell, Wesley C. (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - Moody, Walter S. (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Morgan, Arthur E. (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - Morphy, W. J. (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - Morris, Associations, Robt. (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - Nadler, Marcus (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - National City Bank (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - National Economic League (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - National Foreign Trade Council (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - National Industrial Conference Board (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - New Hampshire, University of (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Norman, C. A. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Olsen, Herluf V. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Patterson, Ernest Minor (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania State College (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Person, Harlow (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Pfleiderer, Emil (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Pigman, Augustus (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Piper, Clarence B. (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Price, Theodore H. (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Rautenstrauch, Walter (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Raymond, Fairfield E. (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Richards, Charles R. (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Richardson, Edward Adams (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Ridgway, Robert (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Roberts, Kenneth Lindsay (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Robinson, Ernest L. (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Roe, Joseph W. (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Rogers, Paul K. (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Rotary Clubs (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Rugg, Earl U. (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Rukeyser, Merryle Stanley (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Sales Management (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - Sawyer, D. H. (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - Schaefer, Otto D. (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Schluter, W. C. (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - Schumpeter, Joseph (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - Schuyler, Montgomery (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Scott, Howard (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - Seabury, George T. (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - Selbert, Mrs. Frieda F. (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Shea, J. J. (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - Shea, William H. (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - Shewhart, W. A. (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - Shoudy, W. A. (Box 75, Folder 40)
    - Siegfried, Thorwald (Box 75, Folder 41)
    - Simon, Arthur (Box 75, Folder 42)
    - Skinner, C. E. (Box 75, Folder 43)
    - Slichter, Charles S. (Box 75, Folder 44)
    - Slichter, Sumner H. (Box 75, Folder 45)
    - Sly, H. Belden (Box 75, Folder 46)
    - Smith, C. E. (Box 75, Folder 47)
    - Smith, Levi P. (Box 75, Folder 48)
    - Smith, Ludlow O. (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - Smoot, Reed (Box 75, Folder 50)
    - Social Science Research Council (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Sonneberg, Walter (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Soule, George R. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Speight, Harold E. B. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Stillwell, L. B. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Street, Clement F. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Survey Graphic (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Taylor Society (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Thompson, Sanford E. (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Thorpe, Merle (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Tonks, Lewi (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Tribit, Charles H. (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Truxal, Andrew G. (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Tuttle, Morton C. (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Twentieth Century Fund (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Vanvechten, George C. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Vermont State Library (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Walsh, David I. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Warren, Glen B. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Washburn, Herbert I. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Waters, W. L. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Weart, Spencer A. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Webster, J. E. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Weiss, C. R. (Box 77, Folder 9)